[woman] ♪ It's Ebony Life ♪
[horn honks]
[man] Sabo Yaba.
[hip-hop music playing
on club PA, muffled]
-[man] Huh?
-[woman] I'll call you later.
[in Pidgin]
You're lucky I'm in a good mood.
Listen to me, Chuks.
You have to stop harassing this girl.
The only men here are our customers.
She will call you when she's done
for the day, so get lost.
Was I talking to you? Huh?
No, but you are crushing our vibe.
Your vibe was crushed many years ago.
Just fuck off.
I'm leaving, but only because I want to.
Come on, girl. Let's go!
Blessing, you don't need this dickhead.
You don't need him.
-Come on, Vanessa.
-You don't need this guy.
Hey, babe. Is that the Johnny guy?
Yes, just ignore him.
[hip-hop music continues]
[in Pidgin] Where are the girls here?
-Ah! My customer.
-Hey.
-Fine boy.
-How are you?
What's up? Where have you been
all my life, handsome?
Where have you been?
I've been here waiting for you.
-Feel like having fun?
-Sure.
But I want something different tonight.
I'm right here for you.
But you know nobody
can satisfy you the way I can.
You can't resist this.
I know, but variety is the spice of life.
Hi, beautiful. What's your name?
Ehi.
Ehi. I like the name.
Let's go have some fun.
Please, I don't need this stress.
Hey, that's okay.
There is no stress. It's an open market.
It's an open market.
If he wants to go with you, go with him.
Who's talking to you?
Enough with the talk. Let's go.
Bitch, I will show you that I'm crazy.
-That's enough. Let her go with him.
-She's taking my customer.
-Let the man choose who he wants.
-Enough of all this.
-No one is asking your dumb opinion.
-Come on, let's have a drink.
[hostess] Sir, welcome.
Yeah, um, give me
one condom and one blue pill.
-Try this one. It's a special product.
-Okay.
You picked the hottest girl. [chuckles]
I'm expecting the result in my body.
Give me the room key.
Okay. Here.
-All right.
-Enjoy yourself.
Let's go. I don't bite.
Unless you want me to. [laughs]
Let's go into the room. Come on.
Come on. We don't have all night.
[door closes]
[sniffs]
-What's wrong with you?
-Nothing. I just want to use the toilet.
-I'll be right back.
-[grunts] Okay.
Hurry up. I am good to go
when this pill kicks in.
[breath quavering]
[quietly] Shit...
[door slams]
Hello? What's going on?
[man] Hello?
[knocking]
Huh? Are you crazy? Come here!
-[shrieking]
-Witch!
Hey!
The crazy bitch has run off.
Catch her for me! Catch her!
[exclaims]
[women chattering, calling out]
[whimpering]
[panting]
Ow!
[people chattering, shouting]
[no audible dialogue]
-[horns honking]
-[man calling out]
[in Pidgin] Anthony-Oshodi!
Oshodi under the bridge!
Oshodi! Anthony-Oshodi!
[continues calling out]
[Afrobeat music playing]
[man singing in African language]
[in Pidgin] Ehi, are you okay?
-[in Pidgin] You have a balance of 500.
-But I still need to pay Chuks.
How is that my business, huh?
He should get you a place to stay then.
If not, you should pay me in full.
I'll pay you tomorrow. I promise.
Hey. You! Come here.
What's wrong with you?
So you went window climbing
and ran away from a paying client?
Are you out of your mind? Do you want them
to chase us out of the hotel?
It was not my fault. The man was crazy.
-She's lying.
-I'm not lying. The man was drunk.
You are too naive
to handle such customers.
Vanessa, fuck off.
After taking my customer,
you ran away, you idiot.
That's enough, Vanessa.
You, leave here.
I don't need your stress.
Please, just sort yourself out.
Just pay your rent on time tomorrow.
So stop climbing through windows
and do your job.
I heard you.
You are too naive for this job!
The next time you touch my customer,
I will deal with you.
[woman]
Keep quiet! You're giving me a headache.
[hip-hop music playing on stereo]
-You okay?
-I'll live.
-Take...
-I don't need it.
It will take the pain away.
[winces]
[sighs]
I mean, this is no life.
[chuckles]
Tell me about it.
I need to leave this place.
-Lagos?
-Nigeria.
I want to go to Europe
where I can make more money.
[sucks teeth]
Do you know anyone
that can help me go to Europe?
Because I am tired of all the guys here.
Hmm. Do you think the guys
over there are better?
-Yes.
-That's a lie. [scoffs]
They are all the same.
[winces]
Let me help you clean that cut up.
Linda, thank you. Thank you very much.
You are welcome.
There is a woman
who takes girls to Europe.
That's why I came to Lagos.
My friend in Benin City told me about her.
So, every month I have to pay her.
Once I pay up in full,
my sister and I are going to Europe
to make a better living for our family.
How much does it cost to go to Europe?
Like $1,200.
Eh? Linda, that's too expensive.
Please, can you talk to the lady for me?
I'd like to go as well.
I could, but the woman
is very secretive about it all.
Please, just try.
It will be a dream come true for me.
Hmm? Please...
[women chattering]
[Afrobeat music playing]
[man singing in African language]
[no audible dialogue]
[woman calls out]
[women chattering]
[in Pidgin] What's up?
Hello, handsome.
Eh?
It's her you want?
Okay.
You are the one he wants.
-Me?
-Yeah, you.
Come on, fuck off.
What's up?
[horns honking]
I can do all sorts of things,
but not everything.
[man] Okay, how much?
It all depends. If it's to play with it
like this, that's 2K.
If it's a blow job like this, 4K.
And a full fuck, 7K.
[man] Do you have a place we can go?
Sure, once you pay,
we will find a place to go.
[man] Get in.
Ah!
Later.
[mutters]
Take care of yourself.
Customer, what the hell
are you doing with this bitch?
Fuck off!
-[Vanessa] Prostitute!
-[Ehi] Whore!
-[siren approaching]
-[all shouting]
[laughing]
[in English] Did I tell you that I was
a very good actress at school?
As long as you know
that this is not the real you
and you are only undercover.
So, how are you?
Okay, I guess.
A few close shaves.
You are going to give me a heart attack.
You are too young for a heart attack.
High blood pressure maybe.
[laughs]
[in Pidgin]
Ah! Ms. Ehi, how are you today?
I'm good.
[sighs]
[woman sniffling]
Why are you down here by yourself?
Eh? Is something wrong?
No. I'm okay.
Ah!
Who did this to you?
Was it Chuks?
Why does he treat you this way?
I caused it. I made him angry.
Blessing, why are you
still hanging out with him?
You don't need him anymore.
Just break up with him.
Eh? Why not just do like other girls
and join all these app things
like Lovers Zone?
He would kill me.
He used to have a lot of girls,
but I'm the only one left.
I'm sure he will kill me
if I try to leave him.
He is heartless.
Thank you. Thank you.
-I will be up soon.
-Are you sure?
Thank you.
Lucky you.
[African highlife music playing]
[man singing in African language]
[in Pidgin] This is the payment
for my sister and I.
Auntie, I hope
she will still be able to go.
-How old is she?
-Seventeen.
-Is she still a virgin?
-Yes.
She has to stay that way.
Thank you, Auntie.
Um, Auntie...
Please, when will we leave
after I make the last payment?
I have no idea. It depends on many things.
But I'll call you once everything is set.
Maybe two days before we go.
Okay, okay. Because I have to bring her
from Benin to Lagos.
That's none of my business.
Once I am ready, there's no turning back.
-What do think you are doing?
-No, no!
Don't push me like that.
Who the hell are you?
[bodyguard]
Madam, I saw this woman spying on you.
What are you looking for here?
Nothing. I was just in my shop
when he started harassing me.
I'm gonna call the cops.
Do you know this girl?
Can't you talk? Do you know her?
Yes. She is my friend.
Did I not tell you not to discuss
this matter with anyone?
-Auntie, I am sorry.
-Auntie, it's not her fault.
I've been the one on her case.
I just want to go to Europe.
I swear, she has not told me anything.
I just followed her here.
-Is this true?
-Yes, Auntie, I swear.
I never told her anything about you.
I swear.
Listen, I hate anyone knowing my business.
Auntie, I am sorry.
I hope you can still help me.
That is not how it works.
You understand me?
It doesn't work like that at all.
Please don't be mad. I'm just desperate.
You need to shut the fuck up.
Just fuck off.
Linda! Linda, please wait.
Linda, please wait.
Did I not promise to discuss
your matter with her?
-Linda, I am so sorry.
-You are crazy!
-Please!
-No! No!
Do you know how much
I have struggled on this matter?
Do you know how much I've paid?
This is my last chance.
Don't fuck it up for me.
Linda, forgive me. Linda!
What? What the fuck are you saying?
How did it happen?
No, no. Don't do this to me.
You told me you were good for it.
Well, you better find another one
because I already told my boss the number.
Fifteen has to be 15.
I don't care. Just do it.
Meet me at the office.
[engine starts]
[horn honking]
[phones ringing]
-[in English] What's happening?
-[Ehi] Have you got a pen?
One sec.
-Hey.
-I met a trafficker today,
a madam who takes people to Europe.
She goes by the name of Alero.
Probably an ex-prostitute.
She drives a Toyota Prado.
Um, registration number KTU447CV.
Just see if there's anything
you can find out about her for me.
All right, stay safe.
Always. Bye.
[knocking]
Who is that?
-It's me, Mummy.
-Hey!
-[in Idoma] How are you?
-I am fine.
Well done, my dear. It's good to see you.
-Thank you, Mum.
-Welcome home.
Sit down.
What can I offer you? Water? Rice?
I already had something to eat.
I insist. I will bring rice anyway.
You can choose not to eat it here.
-Mm-mm.
-Leave me alone. [laughs]
[sighs]
[African '60s pop music playing]
[no audible dialogue]
[in Pidgin] What is this?
It's just some rice I got near the river.
My peace offering. I am so sorry.
Please accept it.
Ah!
This food smells like home-cooked food.
Yes, that's why I bought it for you.
Thank you.
I hope that woman
is not too upset with you.
I think it's all okay. She just called me.
I'm helping her organize girls for a party
at a politician's house tomorrow evening.
-She said to invite you as well.
-Are you serious?
-Are you game?
-Yes.
Thank you.
Chuks! Chuks, please!
Do you know you've overstepped
your boundary? Hmm?
-I'm sorry--
-I've been watching you.
I know you are hiding something. Hmm?
-Hmm?
-[gasping, choking]
I can tell a prostitute when I see one.
And you? [sniffs]
You are no prostitute.
So who are you? Huh?
Who are you? Are you from the police?
-[coughing, gasping]
-[laughs]
I could just kill you right here
and nothing would happen.
You'd just be another dead slut
on the side of the road.
-Please-- Please--
-Hmm?
[gasping]
If you ever tell Blessing
to leave me again, I will kill you.
Do you hear me?
You hear me?
Ladies, I am off to see my customer.
-See you later.
-[woman] Hey, enjoy!
We'll make a lot of money today!
-[laughs] Hey!
-Hey!
-So why can't I come with?
-Sorry, you weren't invited.
Why wasn't I invited?
Maybe she doesn't want your pimp baggage.
[African highlife music playing]
[woman] Hey, hey!
[in Pidgin] Blessing, please step aside.
[song continues]
-[Linda] Good evening, ma.
-Good evening.
Quick, quick, quick.
You guys know the routine.
There will be loads of cash to go around.
And after that, anything goes.
Anything the men want,
you give it to them.
-Is that clear?
-[women] Yes, ma.
Let's go.
[horn honks]
[Afrobeat music playing]
Take care of him.
He's my special customer.
Hmm.
Isn't this our spy?
Please forgive me. I know I messed up.
Yes, you messed up.
I didn't even tell you my name.
My name is Ehi.
You can call me Alero.
Auntie, please,
can you help me get to Europe?
[scoffs]
-You want to go to Europe?
-Yes.
Let's see how you perform tonight.
Then we'll figure it out later.
Come. There is someone
I want to introduce you to.
Sir Phillip, leave politics alone.
I told you I had someone special
to introduce you to.
-[Sir Phillip] Yes.
-[Alero] Mm-hmm.
Ehi, meet Sir Phillip.
He is our host.
Ehi, how are you?
[Ehi] Please to meet you, sir.
[in English]
I can see you will like it here.
[in Pidgin] It's beautiful here.
You haven't even seen the best part of it.
I can take you on a tour.
Would you like that?
I would love that.
Good, good. Let me show you the splendor.
Hmm? And please,
don't call me "Sir Phillip."
You can call me by my name. Phillip.
Ah! It's so beautiful here.
It's an excellent location for a party,
you know,
with an exquisite view of the city.
There's something about Lagos's lights
that gets to me.
It's awesome.
Okay, you, pop it and pour it.
[cork pops]
Ah, here you go.
Excuse me, sir, but I do not drink.
Me too. I don't drink.
It's just that this
is not normal drinking.
This is the finest champagne in the world.
Try it. You'll like it.
Hmm?
Maybe I can...
[exclaims] I am so sorry, sir!
That's okay.
[music continues]
[chattering]
[breathing heavily]
[muttering] What the fuck?
Oh, fuck.
[breath quavering]
[Phillip] Are you all right in there?
Yes, sir!
[deep breath]
[groaning]
[clears throat]
I am not sure what's wrong with me.
I am feeling ill and want to go home.
No worries. I can take care of that.
[cabinet door opens]
[cabinet door closes]
Please, I want to leave.
Wait, at least let the pill
begin to work first, eh?
[African highlife music playing]
♪ Mr. Judge, don't look so mean ♪
♪ Before you talk, I plead not guilty ♪
♪ I said, Mr. Judge, don't look so mean ♪
-[Phillip humming]
-[whimpering]
[whimpering]
Please, sir...
Please, I beg you in the name of God...
Please don't... don't do this to me.
Please.
Please...
[crying]
[sobbing]
[breathing heavily]
[sound fades]
Everything you said and more.
Whew!
What a dream.
And we will be having
another party next month.
Sir Phillip...
I can't wait to see what you will
come up with next. Hmm?
Mwah!
Always a pleasure doing business with you.
Ha! Alero! [chuckles]
Puttana.
Puttana!
[in Pidgin] Wake up. The party is over.
The bus is leaving.
[chattering]
[retching]
[sobbing]
[screams]
[pastor, in English] "Fill me with wisdom,
and I shall be clean.
Wash me and I shall be whiter than snow.
Make me to hear joy and gladness,
and the bones which thou has broken
may rejoice.
Hide thy face from my sins
and blot out all my iniquities.
Create in me a clean heart, O God,
and renew a right spirit within me."
When last did you speak with her?
Yesterday,
before she went for the damn party.
And now she's not responding
to my messages or returning my calls.
Emeka, it's barely 24 hours.
Give it some time
before you begin to panic.
What if something has happened to her?
The longer we wait,
the worse her situation could get.
I'm sure nothing has happened to her.
She's probably just sleeping it off.
Emeka, relax.
In the evening,
go check the normal places.
If you don't find her,
then we'll know there's a problem.
I'm sorry, sir.
I don't think I can wait that long.
If I have to, I'll go to that house. I'll
find out exactly what happened to her.
And what if,
contrary to your expectations,
nothing actually happened to her?
You think she will appreciate
you having blown her cover?
[no audible dialogue]
So this is where you are.
I've been looking around for you.
I have something for you.
What is it?
Come on.
Take it and stop asking questions.
It's your cash from the other night.
Sir Phillip keeps talking about you.
[rap playing on stereo]
Do you still want to go to Europe?
I might have space for you
on my next trip.
When we get there, you'll be
in a group we call forze speciali.
What's that?
It means you will not be standing on
the street like all these common puttane.
You will be escorting important people.
That is what I did.
But if you want to go, you have to pay me.
It's $1,200.
Yes.
Okay.
I'll call you.
-[car door slams]
-[Chuks laughs]
I see you are still interfering
in matters that do not concern you.
Are you talking to me?
Yes, and you heard me.
Stay the fuck out of my business.
Chuks, what are you talking about?
Leave... my... girl. Did you hear me?
[sucks teeth] I'm not here for your girl.
Yeah, right.
I have no interest in your damaged goods.
Wait there and let me show you
what I'm made of.
Be careful.
This guy. Listen, you do not scare me.
Get the fuck out of here.
What's your problem?
I suggest you think carefully
about your next move.
Leave him.
Chuks.
Just in case you are not aware,
you are a dying breed.
The world has moved on without your type.
Your time has passed. This is my time now.
Rest assured,
there is nothing you have that I want.
Vaffanculo!
-Vaffanculo!
-[in English] Motherfucker.
[mutters, sucks teeth]
[Chuks] What do you want?
Can we talk?
Step into my office.
Looks as if you are finally
getting your act together.
How?
Uh-uh.
I thought you wanted to become
one of my girls.
Of course not.
I am here for another reason.
So, what do you want?
Do you know anyone
that can injure someone?
I want to hurt someone badly.
Who is it?
He is really important.
-How important?
-He is a politician.
Hold on.
-What's going on?
-Chuks, can you set it up or not?
Listen, I can.
But these important guys,
they always have a security detail.
It's not worth even trying.
Girl, listen,
anything important people do to you,
just take it as experience.
Learn from the event and let it go.
There is nothing you can do about it.
You see... if you were one of my girls,
I would have protected you.
Excuse me.
The way you protect Blessing, right?
In this, our game,
it's all connected to the Mafia.
My connections are the real Mafia.
In fact,
they are the pioneers of this game.
So if I fuck up, they will kill me.
If you fuck up, I will have to kill you.
-Tony--
-Just let me finish.
If you tell me you have 15 girls
and I let them know
I'm sending 15 girls...
then it has to be 15 girls.
Alero, 15 has to be 15.
Not 14.
-I have 15 girls.
-Mm-hmm.
Because I heard
that one of your girls left.
Yes, but I have replaced her.
Hmm. Let me see her.
[laughing]
This one is forze speciali.
But she looks like trouble.
I've yet to meet a beautiful woman
who's not trouble.
[chuckles]
Has she paid?
She will pay.
Are you sure?
Hmm?
Because it has to be 15 girls.
Fifteen has to be 15.
I'm sure she will pay.
Okay.
[cell phone ringing]
[in Edo]
Good afternoon, Mother. It's me, Linda.
My dear! How is everything in the city?
Everything is fine over here.
Things are falling into place
for me and Beauty.
That is good news. Thank you
very much for doing this for us...
-Not to worry.
-...for our family.
I will continue to pray
for you and your sister.
Thank you. Is Beauty there with you?
-Yes, she is.
-I would like to speak with her.
-Hey, Beauty!
-[Beauty] Yes, Mother?
Come, your sister wants to speak with you.
-Yes, Mother?
-It's your sister.
[in Pidgin] Hello? Linda, how are you?
What's up, Beauty?
Get ready. It's time to come to Lagos.
Okay, I will. I will.
[hip-hop music playing]
I called my sister and told her
I have made all our payments.
[laughs]
She is so happy.
She was just screaming, "Europe! Europe!"
-[laughing]
-[horn honking]
Do you still want to go to Europe?
I'm not sure.
It's a really expensive trip.
[Linda] Yeah, it is.
Which one of you is Ehi?
That's her.
Some guy over there is looking for you.
Very handsome.
Mmm!
Mister, what's up?
[in English] Cut the bullshit.
Why haven't you been answering my calls?
[in Pidgin] Do you want a hand job,
blow job or full fuck?
Just enter the car.
Please.
What is going on?
Are you going to say something or not?
Only if you calm down.
I really can't deal with
any more shouting right now.
Okay.
Oloture.
What happened?
Nothing.
Did something happen at the party?
No.
Then why are you acting strange?
Because I am tired.
Staying awake all day and most
of the night has that effect on me.
How was the party?
Just a party.
Rich people doing what they love to do.
It's over. I need you back at work.
I met the trafficker.
And she has agreed to take me to Europe.
Well, that's...
That's great!
That's what we wanted, right?
This story is not finished.
What are you talking about?
I am saying that there is so much more
to this story that needs to be told,
so many people
that need to be brought down.
Okay, that's it.
I don't know where this is coming from.
I don't know what it is.
But it's not up for conversation anymore.
You're off the story.
Look, Emeka, this is no longer your story.
It is now my story.
And I will get to the end of it
with or without you.
Auntie Alero.
Good afternoon.
-Do I know you?
-My name is Blessing.
I stay at Sandra's house
with Ehi and Linda.
Oh, you're Chuks's girl, right?
-Yes, I am.
-What do you want from me?
-I want to go to the next level.
-No, Blessing! No, no, no.
I have saved up, like, $200.
I will make more soon.
Blessing! No!
Please, I just want
to elevate myself a little. Please!
I don't deal with girls that have pimps.
And you know Chuks is a lunatic,
so I can't help you.
[Alero] Uh-huh.
Don't mind that local puttana.
Oh...
Does that motherfucker want
to mess around with me?
[scoffs]
I will show that bitch
who she is dealing with.
Okay, tomorrow.
We are leaving tomorrow.
Sorry I took so long.
-Where did you go?
-I went to the market.
I'm sorry for coming late.
Chuks, is something wrong?
You know...
I really thought you and I
were really getting on well.
-But we are.
-[grunts]
I'm sure we are getting on well.
[scoffs]
-You're sure?
-I'm sure.
I'm sure.
Are you truly sure?
Yes! Why are you asking me
these sorts of questions?
Because if we were getting on well,
you wouldn't go and see Alero
about going to Europe.
Chuks, I'm sorry...
[crying]
No worries, no worries.
I'll make sure you won't try it again.
-Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
-[whimpering]
Take off this stupid wig.
Very stupid!
[sobbing]
-Beauty!
-Linda!
Where is your bag? Come and show it to me.
Which one?
Look at you! You are now a big girl.
-How is Mum?
-She's fine.
Please.
Come back to me.
I will.
Um...
I want you to keep this for me.
What's this?
It's my report of everything that
has happened while I've been in the house.
Um...
I should get going.
Quick, quick, quick.
Auntie Alero,
this is my sister I told you about.
Get on the bus. Quick, quick, quick.
[man] Move.
Wait, wait. I don't understand.
He was so good at school.
There was no money for him to keep going.
No money? What did you do
with all the money I sent home?
Sister, we used that for food.
After that, there was nothing left.
Don't worry.
As soon as we get to Europe,
we will send more money home. Okay?
Come.
[Oloture's voice]
Chuks is an old-fashioned pimp
who is fast becoming redundant
in the modern world.
Years ago, he would have had many girls,
but times have changed with the Internet,
and apps like Lovers Zone
have replaced men like him.
But desperation creates danger,
and Chuks prowls the pavements
like a hungry bear.
Blessing is Chuks's last girl.
She is an orphan and was abused
by the state since she was a kid.
Broken, bruised and battered,
Blessing cannot escape Chuks's grasp.
He has too much power over her,
and she has nowhere else to go.
And the two of them seem to be
on an inexorable slow train to disaster.
Hurry up, hurry up!
All of you, out of the bus now!
-Bring down your bags.
-[man 2] Come down, come down.
[man] Stop wasting my time!
[man 2] Are you deaf?
Everybody, bring down your bags!
Bring down your bags! Line up!
[man 2] Line up, line up, line up.
[man 1] Take your bags down there
to be searched.
[man 2] Move! Fast! Open up, open up.
All phones here. Put your phones here.
Wait, open them. All right, go.
Open your bag.
-From now till you get to Europe...
-[man 2] Why are you shaking?
...no more communication
with anybody outside.
-Move! You, move!
-[woman shrieks]
-Where is your phone?
-I don't have a phone.
-Why are you lying?
-I don't have a phone, really.
Want me to be ruthless with you?
-No, sir.
-Where is your phone?
-I don't have a phone.
-[man 2] Open it!
[man 1] Now that you are here,
I don't want to hear a word
from any of you.
-I want total silence.
-Move. Move!
We are in control of everything over here.
Am I making myself clear?
-I said, am I making myself clear?
-[women] Yes, sir!
A.
B.
C.
Hey! Come.
A.
[grunts]
B.
Hey!
A.
-She is my sister.
-What did I say before?
You better keep your mouth shut.
I don't care who she is.
Do you hear me?
B!
A!
A.
[Oloture's voice] The last thing
I remembered, he was on top of me,
his breath sour in my face.
I tried to fight him off, but my body was
not working anymore because of the drugs.
The doctor confirmed the next day
that I had been brutally raped.
There was no condom involved.
This is a well-known man, a politician.
His name is Sir Phillip Ondaje.
This is what he does for fun.
He drugs women and then rapes them.
[Oloture's voice, in Pidgin]
You've reached the voice mail of Ehi.
Please leave your message after the tone.
Thank you.
Oh, my goodness, Oloture.
Where are you? Where are you?
You need to come in.
You need to come in immediately.
And please call me once you get this.
What's with all these groups we're in?
I have no idea.
I don't like not being
in the same group as my sister.
It'll be okay.
-Huh?
-Yes.
You don't understand.
She is not street smart like me.
I have to protect her.
See, she's a virgin.
-Huh?
-Yes.
That's why Auntie Alero
agreed to take her.
Auntie, there is some guy here.
He's looking for Ehi.
Sir, Ehi and Linda are not here.
They left today.
Please, do you know where they went?
I have no idea where she is.
They left without warning.
So now I've got to find two new people.
-So, you don't even know--
-I said I don't know anything.
Ask the other girls.
[no audible dialogue]
Customer, you want to have some fun?
Sister, please, I'm looking for Ehi.
Even when the bitch is not here,
she's still ruining business for me.
-[sucks teeth] Please fuck off.
-Please, do you know where she might be?
You're not going to find her.
They have all left for Italy.
-What time did they leave?
-They left this afternoon.
[laughs]
Customer,
did you fall in love with a whore?
I know your type, pretty boy.
You fall in love easily.
Follow me inside. Rest assured,
I'll help you forget Ehi real quick.
Thank you.
Are you seriously rejecting me?
"Thank you"?
You like them cheap, is that it?
That's why you're looking for Ehi.
[buzzes]
Hi.
[Oloture, whispering]
I know you read the stuff,
but I can't talk right now.
-Just listen to me carefully.
-Okay.
I am one hour northwest away from Lagos.
My last turn was Agbara. My sense is we're
going to be here for the next few days.
Hey, listen. We will come and get you.
Okay, but I have to go now.
I love you.
I have to go. Bye.
Posture is very important in Europe.
You need to stand straight.
See how I stand?
Make sure all your God-given assets
are not hidden.
You want them on display.
You, let me see your stomach.
Open. Let me see.
Uh-huh.
All your tette and your culo
must be on display.
This is how you will earn
loads of money in Europe.
[all] Yes, ma.
Take a good look at her.
She is what we call forze speciali.
And if you want to become forze speciali,
its time to learn.
-Do you understand?
-Yes, ma.
You, walk for us.
Shake them. They're your God-given assets.
With them, you'll make your money.
Can you see her? Take a good look at her.
Come back. You, you're next.
Okay, this one's an expert.
Nothing to teach there.
You come over here.
Hey! Look here.
You, the one who looked down!
Come over here.
Can you lap dance?
Don't look so worried. It's no big deal.
Just make sure
your pussy touches his dick.
I'm not going to repeat myself!
So, show me what you can do.
Bring your ass here.
As attractive as she is,
why is she behaving like this?
Move your ass sideways.
-Sheriff, can you feel her pussy?
-I can't feel shit.
Will you do it properly!
Sheriff, show her how to do it.
-Grind!
-[sobbing]
-Let her feel your dick.
-She is highly satisfying.
Okay, step aside.
All right, babe, step aside.
You! Hey! Come over here.
Why are you frowning?
-Why are you in a hurry?
-This one looks like an expert.
-Yes, she does know. I can feel it.
-She is a professional.
Go gently.
Sheriff, hold her waist.
She's so good, in fact, I'm confused.
That's enough. Step aside.
Get up. You're too emotional.
That one did too much.
[Victor]
Now, where is that girl with the big ass?
This is an emergency.
I have one of my staff members in there.
She's a journalist
with more bravery than sense.
I need to get her out.
I hear you, Mr. Okoye.
All my men are out there
on special operations today.
It's not possible.
When is the earliest you're able to go?
Well, um...
if everything in your story
checks out, um,
the absolute earliest would be
dawn tomorrow morning.
[no audible dialogue]
[chanting in African language]
[laughing]
[continues incantation]
[chicken squawking]
Yes.
Yes. It is well.
That is it.
[resumes incantation]
[chattering]
[chanting incantation]
[shrieks]
[toilet flushes]
So you like to drug and rape
young women, huh?
Excuse me?
I'm the editor of The Scoop.
I know you, and I know what you do.
Jo-- [grunting]
I'm coming for you and your sick friends.
Prick.
I, Ehi, do swear by [indistinct]...
...that if I dare cross my sponsors...
...I'll find myself in the coffin...
...and so shall it be.
[officer] We have confirmed
from our colleagues in the police.
We will have a task force
for dawn tomorrow.
Thank you. Thank you, thank you!
Thank you very much.
You won't be sorry about this, I promise.
I need you to leave, Mr. Okoye.
Yeah.
I suppose I'm not allowed
to join you for the operation tomorrow?
No. It's an official operation.
Definitely not.
Right. Thank you.
Thank you.
Next.
Auntie, can I read the contract
before signing?
Of course. I'll give you ten seconds
to read it, and then you'll sign it.
-Any problem?
-No.
Sign.
Auntie, when do we travel?
When it's time, we will leave. Next!
[Linda] What's up?
-Who did you get?
-Huh?
-Who'd you get?
-Wachuka Otieno from Kenya.
Mine is Thandie Zwane from South Africa.
Listen, I want to ask you something.
What is it?
[whispering] Let me borrow your phone.
But I don't have a phone.
-You have a phone.
-No, I do not.
You have a phone.
I saw it the other night.
-I don't.
-Yes.
I just want to call my mum quickly.
I didn't know we wouldn't be able
to have our phones.
No. No.
I just want her to know
that Beauty and I are okay.
-Please.
-But it's not safe.
I swear, I will be on the phone
for less than 30 seconds.
[scoffs]
Please.
Please be very careful.
Trust me, I will. Trust me. Please.
I'll put it under your pillow
when everyone is asleep.
Okay. Thank you.
[cell phone ringing]
[in Edo] Who is calling me so late?
-Hello?
-Hello, Mama.
Please don't be offended.
I won't be able to talk for long now.
Thank God you called. How is your trip?
My mind is not at peace.
How is Beauty? I hope she's okay.
Beauty is fine. I can't talk now.
I will let you know when I can talk.
What are you doing? You are very stupid!
Give me that phone!
[Linda whimpering]
[Victor] Get out of here!
Get out!
All of you, wake up now
and get out to the pool. Now!
Out! Can't you hear me? Move!
Now! Run, run, run.
What did I say about phones?
What did I say!
I said no phones.
I said anyone caught with a phone
would be dealt with.
Not only does she have a phone,
she has been spying on us.
No.
Using it to send information
about where we are.
No. No.
[whimpering] No.
-[Oloture] Linda.
-No!
-[Beauty] Please, no.
[screaming]
Quiet!
Everybody, get ready.
Get ready. Go pack your things.
We have to leave right now.
[exclaims] Move!
Why did you have to kill her?
She was sending information
about our operations. Who is she?
What if she is from the police?
-I don't know.
-Look, it's your job to know.
You're supposed
to investigate all these things.
-I did all the checks I'm supposed to do.
-You didn't do them well enough.
I swear, this better all just go away.
If not, it's your head.
-Do you know where her family lives?
-Of course I know.
We need to send them a strong message
so they know who they're messing with.
-Heavy.
-[man] Yes, boss?
[whimpering, crying]
Beauty, please get changed.
Please!
-Bring those girls.
-Okay, boss.
Both of you move. Up!
-Stand up and follow me!
-[man] Stand up. Move! I said move!
Avoid their faces,
in case we still need them.
What do you know about the phone?
This one's a bush girl. Get her out
of my face. She doesn't know anything.
This one...
I'm not too sure about this one.
What do you know about the phone?
-I don't know anything.
-I said, what do you know about the phone?
[whimpering] I know nothing.
I said, what do you know about the phone?
[sobbing] Nothing.
You don't know anything, right?
-You don't know anything, right?
-I know nothing.
Do you think I'm playing here?
What do you know about the phone?
-[sobbing]
-Do you think I am a fool?
Are your crazy?
What do you know about the phone?
You want to ruin my business. Is that it?
You want to ruin my business?
You don't want to talk?
You don't want to talk. Is that it?
[horn honks]
[tires squealing]
What happened?
Well, it looks like they got away
before we got here.
They must have been tipped off.
They left in a hurry.
Where will they go now?
Go to the poolside
at the back of the house.
There's a body lying there.
Check if it's not your reporter.
[street vendors calling out]
[calling out]
Ah, Mr. Victor! Hey! You are welcome.
-Hey.
-[laughs] Mr. Victor.
-How are you?
-I'm well, thank you.
-How is our business?
-Are you game?
We are always ready.
I come with the usual.
I trust you.
Hey! Hey!
Where are you going?
-I need the toilet.
-I need to shit.
We are about to cross the border
and you guys need to go shit!
Okay, go now. Quickly!
Fast, no time. Let go of her hand!
Keep moving.
Go this way.
Move!
[chattering]
What are you taking across the border?
There is nothing illegal in there?
Open the boot of the car.
Let me see what you have there.
I said you should go back, but you are
bold enough to walk up to me, right?
Listen, I am a journalist. As a matter of
fact, this is a matter of life and death.
It is very important. My staff is there.
I really need to be there.
Please understand my point.
It's not for you to understand.
Get in your car and join the queue.
-Help! Help!
-Help us!
Help me! Help us!
-Please!
-Go, Beauty! Go!
Help! Someone help!
[horns honking]
Where the hell did she run off to?
What kind of nonsense is that?
What's going on here?
See, I am trying-- I am a journalist.
There's a very serious emergency
I need to attend to.
As a matter of fact,
somebody's life is at stake.
This place is a military zone.
-I understand that!
-Go back. I said go back!
Can you please just...
-Okay, just calm down.
-Go back!
Just try to listen to me
and understand what I'm trying to say.
You-- You're not even--
What the--
[hip-hop song playing]
[African funk music playing]